# IETTA A G U S T Í N

PRODUCT DESIGNER



#### CONTACTO

agustinfrancoietta@gmail.com

1154656277

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

#### EDUCATION

2021 - PRESENT

#### Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

Diplomatura en Accesibilidad y Usabilidad

0 2013 - 2019

#### Universidad de Buenos Aires

Diseñador de Imagen y Sonido

# COURSES

2022

#### **Comfy Languages**

IT roadmap B1, English.

2018 - 2020

#### Coder House

UX/UI course

**UX** Writing course

Web development course

Programming course

#### PROFILE

Product Designer with almost 3 years of experience in UX and a huge background in graphic and audiovisual design.

I love to work with different roles in UX and other tech professionals. I'm always learning new things with my favourite music in background.

#### EXPERIENCE

O 3/2021 - PRESENT

# **Product Designer at Banco Galicia**

I'm Product Designer in Galicia's design team. I'm responsable of all the user's benefits, from promotions webs to Quiero! fidelity program.

06/2021 - PRESENT

## **UX/UI Professor at Coder House**

I love to teach and help new designers!
I'm teaching UX/UI online course for 60 students.

08/2020 - 03/2021

# **UX/UI** Designer at BP4

I worked in a software factory as a UX/UI Designer.

I design dashboards for web apps and hybrid mobile apps, from the research in the beginning of the project to the end, delivering high fidelity prototypes.

02/2020 - PRESENT

# Product Designer en GorillaSite

Nowadays, i'm a consultant in Gorillasite to improve and design our own product, a headless CMS.

Also, I work in freelance projects, UX/UI web apps and web pages's redesign.